# **Nguyen Minh Huy**

**DOB** 03/21/1993

**Gender** Male

**Phone** 0123-810-7765

Email huynm2103@gmail.com

Address 13, Bui Si Tiem Street, Thai Binh city, Thai Binh



#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

I am passionate about IT and I can quickly learn a new programming language or a new technique. For teamworking, I am an open-minded individual and I can work well with others team-members. I can work well in both role, as a member or team-leader. I have experience in developing ASP.NET web and have good understanding about OOP and MVC framework.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Sep 2015 - Now	FPT University - Capstone Project  Developer - Develop the Website by ASP.NET MVC 5 and AngularJS framework Create design for Admin - Create and execute project work plans
Apr 2014 - Dec 2014	Newwave Solution JSC  Developer  - Develop the cross platform game, the web by Cocos2d-JS,  Wordpress framework.  - Communicate directly to client for requirements.

#### **EDUCATION**

Oct 2011 - Now	FPT University
	Software Engineer

#### **CERTIFICATIONS AND AWARDS**

Nov 03, 2015	Honorable Student Of Semester - Fpt University
Jun 29, 2015	Level 5 - Summit 1 (5.0 IELTS)
Jun 12, 2015	Honorable Student Of Semester - Fpt University

## **SKILLS**

Languages	English, Japanese
Programming	PHP, Java, C, C++ (Basic) C#
	HTML, JavaScript, CSS3
Operating System	Window
IDE	PhpStorm, NetBeans, Visual Studio 2013
Framework	ASP.NET MVC 3 or higher AngularJS
	WordPress
	Cocos2d-JS
	Bootstrap 3
	JQueryMobile

#### **PROJECTS**

## **Website DANDELION**

(Sep 01, 2015 - Now)

Customer	FPT University
Description	Dandelion is a major platform for crowdfunding. Anybody could launch a project on Dandelion as long as it follows our rules. We believe that creative projects making a better world, and we're thrilled to help support new ones. Building a community of backers around an idea is an amazing way to make something new.
Team size	6
My position	Developer
My responsibility	Develop the back end and the front end for website. Create design for admin.
Technologies used	ASP.NET MVC 5, AngularJS 1.4.7, Bootstrap 3, SQL Server 2012

# Android Application KAOUI (Oct 01, 2014 - Dec 30, 2014)

Customer	Japanese
Description	Develop Mobile UI for the customer android application.
Team size	4
My position	Developer
My responsibility	Develop the front end of the application.
Technologies used	jQueryMobile, Bootstrap 3

#### **Website FELICE**

(Aug 01, 2014 - Sep 30, 2014)

- 1	
- 1	
- 1	

Customer	Japanese
Description	A insurance company need a new website. My team make a website by WordPress and migrate data from old their website.
Team size	5
My position	Developer
My responsibility	Develop the back end and the front end for website.
Technologies used	WordPress, Bootstrap 3, jQuery 1.8.3

# **Game Maikibun**

(Jun 01, 2014 - Jul 30, 2014)

Customer	Japanese	
Description	A organization need a card game for kids. This game have 2 kinds of cards: supermen and monsters. User have to win 6 monsters to win this game.	
Team size	4	
My position	position Developer	
My responsibility	Develop the game by Cocos2d-JS	
Technologies used	nologies used Cocos2d-JS, CakePHP, PostgreSQL	

# Game Gacha

(Apr 01, 2014 - Jun 30, 2014)

Customer	Japanese
Description	In this game, user have to buy tickets by real money. With 1 ticket, User have a chance to win a prize (1 in 7 prizes).
Team size	4
My position	Developer
My responsibility	Develop the game by Cocos2d-JS
Technologies used	Cocos2d-JS, PostgreSQL, Nodejs